So he's going to be opening up for Ricochet in Ricochet and then we'll have some travel
stuff going on before hand or in the air, opening ceremony so we've got vendors and food
trucks and bounce houses and kids owned and how much stuff going on so yes sir.
Just what I had the Friday night at the bottom of the bar with you got the Disney video of you.
I think you got that.
I'm not always amazing, but it smells really good.
Good stuff.
Some of the stuff I have.
I guess I'll get the next time.
Been in the back of my island.
He's been in Iceland for a week.
His hands were really cold.
We got it.
But the root 66 nails is big for our community.
You know.
That's successful.
Yeah.
They had the rags at the wrong last week with truck show.
And it was a successful event and that event will be moving next year.
It looks like and we're moving from Buffel Run to Main Street and we'll actually have rags on
the root.
So there's a truck show.
There's no truck shows on root 66 anywhere in the country that we know of.
So this would be the first one.
So.
And so we got a lot of stuff happening in our girls with CVB.
Other genies care now.
Do them good job.
So come out for the root 66 area and excited to special next week.
It's all you got.
Now we're going to 14 city manager communications.
Just like bus said we have to hear it's best.
Make sure they're 10.
Also a couple other things.
I would like to you know.
Mystery.
He's got a lot of heat but I.
I mean he was he has done some behind the scenes of my understanding.
So we'd like to say thank you.
because we were going to have to ask the county for some help on this break grain, or not the break grain, but this grain, so we want to make sure everybody's working together, so he was very kind of calling me this evening and say, hey, we got some stuff coming, it's going to come out, so I do want to say thank you to you on that.
Lastly, I said today on the bridge, we have over $10 million in grants in the last two years, and I would love to put any city archives up against that. I mean, that's huge.
Like I said, at the bridge, use a Taylor Swift line, and we're in a grants area, and don't like it's fine to use Taylor Swift as if you were in a grants area.
You know, I want to say to you, you know, these guys go and have these grants, like they are for a community, our size, they're extreme, they're extreme and important, but they're really, really competitive.
So we're swinging an arrow on a linkswing at and see what we can get, so I don't know these guys will keep pursuing them, so we appreciate it. We're a finalist in another large.
Yeah, and this one we just got was my I was largest and if we get the one that he's talking about it'll be the mine was long
So they're getting their own efforts and good stuff
That I have all right 15 a German motion to prove second
Thank you all